wealth is a necessity at every stage of
Life enabling you to fulfill your dreams
secure your future and provide financial
protection for your loved ones with the
ICICI Pro protect and gain plan you can
confidently navigate your financial
Journey knowing you are on the path to
Prosperity our growth variant is
designed to supercharge your wealth
creation and help achieve your dreams
whether you are saving for a big
purchase or a
payment ICICI Pro protect and gain
growth can help you get there with
multiple benefits including potential to
build your wealth through Market linked
returns providing flexibility to invest
across a diverse range of funds tailored
to your financial goals while allowing
you to switch between equity debt and
balanced funds depending on how much
risk you are willing to take through
fixed portfolio strategy offering a life
cover of up to 40 times of the
annualized premium with optional Riders
of accidental death and disability cover
along with tax benefits to maximize your
savings so while wait Kickstart your
wealth creation Journey today with ICICI
Pro protect and Game Plan
[Music]